(slow electronic music)
(rock music)
(crowd cheering)
♪ Oooo ♪
♪ We're leavin' together ♪
♪ But still it's farewell ♪
♪ And maybe we'll come back ♪
♪ To Earth, who can tell ♪
♪ I guess there is no one to blame ♪
♪ We're leaving ground ♪
♪ Leaving ground ♪
♪ Will things ever be the same again ♪
♪ It's the final countdown ♪
♪ The final countdown ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ We're headin' for Venus ♪
♪ And still we stand tall ♪
♪ 'Cause maybe they've seen us ♪
♪ And welcome us all, yeah ♪
♪ With so many light years to go ♪
♪ And things to be found ♪
♪ To be found ♪
♪ I'm sure that we all miss her so ♪
♪ It's the final countdown ♪
♪ The final countdown ♪
♪ Final countdown ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ (guitar solo) ♪
♪ The final countdown ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ It's the final countdown ♪
♪ The final countdown ♪
♪ (echos) ♪